Jhal
Hello Hello Viewers Welcome to my YouTube
channel. In this video we are going to
see the technical knowledge of Face Loot General Insurance Company. We will
also see what target the brokerage house has set. If you have not subscribed to the channel yet, then
subscribe to the channel so that you will keep getting the
latest videos related to that stock on this channel. So let's
start by
looking at its minister's chart, you can see it here, it is continuing
inside friend, it is going
upwards in the
entire here, Stark made a high here till 1627
and it has also been seen at the level of 12, it
is trading at Rs. 1265 in 2014 and this 12 sugar level
here, you can see that you had moused over it earlier also by taking support
and this
project which was made in toe, while
making training of a friend, it went upwards, that is, I did
not black it here, I continued playing with my hand
and this is 1400 friends, its
low for the first time is swing  It is low, I did a
one there and within 1 hour
it has converted here.
After clicking this look, guys, I just saw that the
14 sugar level was the support here,
now the distance has been created for it, so that
sugar level and here after the fall, you can
see a retracement at this level
and you will again
see a soldier at this number because the
projection is that after the fresh fall, you will
see an unknown soldier. So
now by creating a pattern of this type here, the stock can go back upwards
or this topic is by
creating a pattern of continuation Nashik dont, those who
are there can also play
and you can also see the Gyaraspur level board here, the
next point is its thousand level, this
target can also be seen, only then
after the continuation retracement, it will
come for the fall, so for now, your
website will come in the address here, so its
point is reached in the short term on the military tank at 527,
so how can you take advantage of that,
for this you can see it on the whisker daily chart.  If we
take it from the drain, then here we have to
see a double pot forming here, you can see that
Stark had taken support earlier at the same level and this
time also, that is why
Bhaskar is trying to take support versus break, so I can see that there is an
association level here twice,
you can see that Stark has wasted multiple times here, so
Paras and Shri Ghanshyam
are airport and if it presses this then we
can press media bank and our
incident will be of Rs 1325
because the stock had taken support here earlier
and you can see that now it can
work as resistance for it and if it
breaks this then our next target will be of
Rs 14100 or so
for the short term here we can have two
targets, you can see that if it
presses this then it will take its mentor, if
it does not break then it can be
seen as below and by
clicking on the low of ignorance, we
can see this low, but the
charts here are the most  Probably, you have
seen its side effects,
they can get half of their value in Great
because it has tested this level for a long time,
now this house brokerage houses can
watch it live on Facebook, so here you can see
its target in the championship when it was
given in Solapur and this article is of
March 25, 2019, so guys if it has to
achieve the target of 16%, which you can see is at
this level, it is near the high, so you
can see it here, the resistances that have been
made for it, you can see those legs and here, after doing
multiple time test, one has to do one
here, this is the average resistance, if the
selling will come, if Maha Vishnu Sainik keeps going
up after testing, then you can see
1600 level or new
vitamins here, so for now,
if seen in soft, then
in a hotel above Varanasi, you can
see a target of 728%,
so the test that has to be done with onion in this will have an
effect of three to four% and
before trading in this, do 47 yourself once.
And if you
liked the video then like it and if you want to follow the channel then
subscribe. Thank you so much.